{
    "id": "c6c4517765c249b68d1337f9167c42ed",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The three brothers love ………………………….",
            "description": "Each other refers to two people one another refers to more than two people.",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The husband and the wife should love and respect ………………………….",
            "description": "Each other refers to two people one another refers to more than two people.",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let …………………………… go now.",
            "description": "Let is a verb. A pronoun used as the object of a verb should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are not as intelligent as ……………………………",
            "description": "Object pronouns are common after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither answer ………………………….. correct.",
            "description": "We use a singular verb after either and neither. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is smarter than …………………………….",
            "description": "Object pronouns are common after than. Subject pronouns are also possible with a verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "I am",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "People suffer when ………………………….. do not have money.",
            "description": "We use they to refer to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "we",
                "they"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy …………………………….. of movies.",
            "description": "Use this with kind and these with kinds.",
            "answers": [
                "this kind",
                "these kinds",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not trust these ………………………….. of people",
            "description": "Use kinds and sorts with these and those.",
            "answers": [
                "kind",
                "kinds",
                "sorts"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. a rainy day, we stayed inside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Being",
                "It being"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My essay is better than ………………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my friend",
                "that of my friend",
                "my friends",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my car. Is that ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}